Evil has a whole new rap!
Leprechaun: Back 2 tha Hood is a horror, comedy
film directed by Steven Ayromlooi.
When Emily Woodrow and her friends happen on a treasure chest full of gold coins, they fail to to heed the warnings of a wise
old psychic who had foretold that they would encounter trouble with a very nasty and protective Leprechaun.
Leprechaun, played by Warwick Davis.
Emily, played by Tangi Miller.
Rory, played by Laz Alonso.
Jamie, played by Page Kennedy.
Lisa, played by Sherrie Jackson.
Esmerelda, played by Donzaleigh Abernathy.
Leprechaun: Back 2 tha Hood (also known as Leprechaun 6) is a 2003 American black comedy-horror film written and directed by Steven
Ayromlooi, and a standalone sequel to Leprechaun in the Hood (2000) with no returning characters or references made to that film.
It is the sixth installment of the Leprechaun series, and the
last entry to star Warwick Davis in the title role.
The film has the villainous leprechaun rampaging through an urban area and killing anyone in his path while looking
for his gold, which was stolen by a group of youths who are using it to fulfill their wildest dreams.
It is the first film in the series to be released by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of sequel, leprechaun, slasher.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.